<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Air Cargo Shipping Guidelines</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="tanya_regis">Do Not Have An Account? </string>
    <string name="registrasi">Register Now</string>
    <string name="persetujuan">I Am Responsible That The Data I Entered Is Correct</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="linkdg"><u>www.dgregulations.com</u></string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="type_name">Type Name</string>
    <string-array name="spinner_gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--judul-judul-->

    <string name="judul_class1">Class 1 - Explosive</string>
    <string name="judul_class2">Class 2 - Gases</string>
    <string name="judul_class3">Class 3 - Flammable Liquid</string>
    <string name="judul_class4">Class 4 - Flammable Solid</string>
    <string name="judul_class5">Class 5 - Oxidizing Substance and Organic Peroxides</string>
    <string name="judul_class6">Class 6 - Toxic and Infectious Substance</string>
    <string name="judul_class7">Class 7 - Radioactive Material</string>
    <string name="judul_class8">Class 8 - Corrosive</string>
    <string name="judul_class9">Class 9 - Miscellaneous Dangerous Goods</string>
    <string name="judul_handling">Handling Label</string>

    <string name="judul_subclass11">Class 1.1</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass12">Class 1.2</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass13">Class 1.3</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass14">Class 1.4</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass15">Class 1.5</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass16">Class 1.6</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass21">Class 2.1</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass22">Class 2.2</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass23">Class 2.3</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass41">Class 4.1</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass42">Class 4.2</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass43">Class 4.3</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass51">Class 5.1 Oxidizer</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass52">Class 5.2 Organic Peroxides</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass61">Class 6.1 Toxic Substance</string>
    <string name="judul_subclass62">Class 6.2 Infectious Substance</string>

    <string name="isi_dg">
         Dangerous goods are articles or subtances which are capable of posing a significant risk to health, safety or to property when transported by air.
    </string>

    <!--classification-->

    <string name="isi_class1">
        Explosives (substances that are not explosives but which can form explosive atmospheres gas, vapor or dust are not included in class 1).
        Except which is too dangerous for transportation or place of dominant danger in accordance with other classes.
        Explosives, except devices containing explosives in such quantities or characters, so that accidental or accidental ignition or initiation during transport will have no external effects either through projection, fire, smoke, heat or loud noise.
        Class 1 has the following divisions:
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class2">
        Gas is a substance that At 50°\ C has a vapor pressure of more than 300 kPa or has actually become gas at 20°\ C at a normal pressure of 101.3 kPa.
        The gas sent can be: \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 1. Compressed gas \n
        \t\t\t\t 2. The liquefied gas \n
        \t\t\t\t 3. Gas cooled \n
        \t\t\t\t 4. The dissolved gas \n
        \t\t\t\t 5. Solidified gas \n\n
        There are 3 Division of Gasses :
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class3">
        The purpose of flammable liquid is flammable liquid and this class has no sub-division, but has its own characteristics and specific packing levels, as follows: \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class4">
        In class 4 it discusses about dangerous and flammable solid-shaped items. Class 4 is divided into 3 divisions.
        Packing Group Criteria: \n\n
        \t\t\t\t - PG 1: If the substance reacts with water strongly at ambient temperature and generally indicates a tendency for the gas to be produced to spontaneously ignite, or that reacts readily with water at room temperature so that the rate of evolution of flammable gases is equal to or greater than 10 l/kg Substance for one minute. \n
        \t\t\t\t - PG 2: If a substance / goods reacts to liquids / water with evolution greater than 20 l/kg hour and does not satisfy PG 1 or PG 2 criteria. \n
        \t\t\t\t - PG 3: If a substance or substance reacts slowly to liquid or water and the reaction is less than 1 l/kg hourly and does not meet critically PG 1 or PG 2. \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class5">
        In this fifth class explain about substances and peroxide goods that easily produce flammable O2 or increase the risk of fire hazard in contact with other combustible goods.
        There are two divisions in this class, namely:
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class6">
        This class describes items that contain toxins and formulations that can cause acute health damage and even death at certain concentrations if contaminated by humans.
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class7">
        Radioactive material means any material containing radionuclides where both the activity concentration.
        These regulations do not apply to any of the following : \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 1. Radioactive material implanted or incorporated into a person or live animal for diagnosis or treatment \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 2. Radioactive material in or on a person who is to be transported for medical treatment because the person has been subject to accidental or deliberate in take of radioactive material or to contamination, taking into account the necessary radiological protection measure with respect to other passengers and crew, subject to approval by the operator. \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 3. Radioactive material in consumer products which have received regulatory approval, following their sale to the end user. \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 4. Non-radioactive solid objects with radioactive substances present on any surfaces in quantities not in excess of the limit specified in the definition of contamination \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class8">
        Substances which by chemical action, can cause severe damage when in contact wth living tissue or, in the case of leakage will materially damage or even destroy, other goods or the means of transport.
        These tabel for packing group Assignment based on Corrosivity :
    </string>
    <string name="isi_class9">
        Articles and substance which, during air transport, present a danger not covered by other classes.
        Class 9 includes, but is not limited to the following articles and substances : \n\n
        1. Aviation Regulated Solid or Liquid \n
        \t\t\t\t Any material which has narcotic, noxious, irritating or other properties such that, in the event of spillage or leakage on aircraft, could cause extreme annoyance or discomfort to crew members  so as prevent the correct performance of assigned duties.
        The materials included under this proper shipping name must not meet any of the definitions for classes 1 through 8. \n\n
        2. Magnetized material \n
        \t\t\t\t Any material which, when packed for air transport, has a maximum magnetic field strength sufficient to cause a compass deflection of more than 2 degrees at a distance of 2.1 m from any point on the surface of the assembled package. \n\n
        3. Elevated temperature substance \n
        \t\t\t\t Substance that are transported or offered for transport at temperatures equal to or exceeding 100°C in a liquid state  or at temperatures equal or exceeding 240°C in a solid state. \n\n
        4. Lithium Batteries \n
        \t\t\t\t Cells and batteries , cells and batteries contained in equipment, or cells and batteries packed with equipment containing lithium in any form must be assigned to UN 3090, UN 3091, 3480, or 3481 as appropriate. \n\n
        Miscellaneous Articles and substance : \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 1. Asbestos \n
        \t\t\t\t 2. Capacitors \n
        \t\t\t\t 3. Carbon dioxide \n
        \t\t\t\t 4. Consumer commodity \n
        \t\t\t\t 5. Chemical and first aid kits \n
        \t\t\t\t 6. Life saving appliance \n
        \t\t\t\t 7. Vehicle \n
        \t\t\t\t 8. Zinc dthionite \n
    </string>

    <!--labelling-->

    <string name="isi_11">
        Has a mass explosion hazard (mass burst is one that affects almost the entire load almost instantaneously). \n\n
        Name : Explosive \n
        Cargo IMP code : REX, RCX, RGX, as applicable \n
        Symbol Exploding Bomb (Black) – Background Orange \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_12">
        Has a projection hazard but not a mass explosion hazard. \n\n
        Name : Explosive \n
        Cargo IMP code : REX, RCX, RGX, as applicable \n
        Symbol Exploding Bomb (Black) – Background Orange \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_13">
        Has a fire hazard and the danger of minor explosions or minor projection hazards or both, but not the danger of a mass explosion. This division consists of articles and substances that: \n\n
        \t\t\t - Generates a large enough heat, or \n
        \t\t\t - Burning one after the other, producing a small explosion and / or projection effect. \n\n
        Name : Explosive \n
        Cargo IMP code : REX, RCX, RGX, as applicable \n
        Symbol Exploding Bomb (Black) – Background Orange \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_14">
        The effect is largely limited to this package and no projection of fragments with size or range is large enough to be expected. External fire should not cause an instantaneous burst of almost the entire package contents. \n\n
        Name : Explosive \n
        Cargo IMP code : RXB, RXC, RXD, RXE, RXG, RXS as applicable \n
        Figures (Black) – Background Orange \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_15">
        Very insensitive material that has a danger of mass explosion. \n\n
        Name : Explosive \n
        Cargo IMP code : REX as applicable \n
        Figures (Black) – Background Orange \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_16">
        Highly insensitive material that does not have a mass explosion hazard. \n\n
        Name : Explosive \n
        Cargo IMP code : REX as applicable \n
        Figures (Black) – Background Orange \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_21">
        Gas with 20C and normal pressure 101.3 kPa. \n\n
        Name : Flammable Gas \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RFG \n
        Symbol Flame (Black or White) Background Red \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_22">
        - Gases that can cause shortness of breath in the form of liquid gas and can replace the function of air in the atmosphere \n
        - Is an oxidizer, a gas which generally can provide oxygen, cause or contribute to the burning of other materials more than air. \n\n
        Name : Non-Flammable Gas, non Toxic Gas \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RNG or RCL for Cyrogenic Liquids \n
        Symbol Gas Cylinder (Black or White) Background Green \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_23">
        - Known to be highly toxic or corrosive to humans to pose a health hazard \n
        - Considered to be toxic or corrosive to humans because it has a value equal to or less than 5000 ml/m3 when tested. \n\n
        Name : Toxic Gas \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RPG \n
        Symbol Skull and Crossbone (Black) Background White \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_30">
        Name : Flammable Liquids \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RFL \n
        Symbol Flame (Black or white) Background Red \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_41">
        Flammable solid self reactive substance.
        This division explains about solids that can be activated or burned on their own which can threaten flight safety.
        An example of this class is matches. \n\n
        Name : Flammable Solid \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RFS \n
        Symbol Flame (Black) White with seven vertical red stripes \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_42">
        Substance liable to spontaneous combustion.
        This division explains about solids that can be activated or burned on their own when in the open air.
        Examples of substances from this class are Magnesium diamide. \n\n
        Name : Spontaneously Combustible \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RSC \n
        Symbol Flame (Black) Upper half white lower half red \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_43">
        Substance dangerous when wet.
        This division explains about solids that can be activated and burned on their own if they have water.
        An example of this class is carbide. \n\n
        Name : Dangerous When Wet \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RFW \n
        Symbol Flame (Black or white) Blue \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_51">
        Oxidizer is a substance that easily oxidizes with other substances. An example of this substance is bleaches (bleach). \n\n
        Name : Oxidizer \n
        Cargo IMP Code : ROX \n
        Symbol Flame over Cycle (Black) Background Yellow \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_52">
        Organic peroxides are goods or substances made from a combination of two oxygen and oxygen structures.
        It may assist or facilitate the combustion process if exposure to fire or heat can result in an explosion.
        If it reacts with other materials then the danger will be greater, the decomposition of this material can produce toxic and combustible gas. \n\n
        Name : Organic Peroxide \n
        Cargo IMP Code : ROP \n
        Symbol Flame (Black or white) Background Upper half red, lower half yellow \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_61">
        Toxic substance is a toxic substance that can cause danger even to death for humans if contacted through swallowing, touching, or inhalation.
        Division 6.1 has a hazard classified as follows: \n\n
        Name : Toxic \n
        Cargo IMP Code RPB \n
        Symbol Skull and Crossbone Black background White \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_62">
        This division describes items that are easily infected by pantogen and other organism\' s micro content and can cause death to living things.
        Examples of this class are viruses, and bacteria. \n\n
        Name : Infectious Substance \n
        Cargo IMP Code RIS \n
        Symbol Three Crescents superimposed on a circle and inscription Black Background White \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_71">
        Name : Radioactive \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RRW \n
        Minimum dimensions : 100 x 100 mm \n
        Symbol (trefoil): Black \n
        Background : White \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_72">
        Name : Radioactive \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RRY \n
        Minimum dimensions : 100 x 100 mm \n
        Symbol (trefoil) : Black \n
        Background : Top half yellow with white border, bottom half white \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_73">
        Name : Radioactive \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RRY \n
        Minimum dimensions : 100 x 100 mm \n
        Symbol (trefoil) : Black \n
        Background : Top half yellow with white border, bottom half white \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_74">
        Minimum dimensions : 100 x 100 mm \n
        Text (Mandatory): "FISSILE" in black on white in upper half of label \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_80">
        Name : Corrosive \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RCM \n
        Minimum Dimensions ; 100 x 100 mm \n
        Symbol (liquids spilling from two glass vessels and attacking a hand and metal) : Black \n
        Background : Upper half white, lower half black with white border \n
    </string>

    <string name="isi_90">
        Name : Miscellaneous \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RMD or ICE, RLI, RLM, RSB \n
        Minimum Dimensions : 100 x 100 m \n
        Symbol : seven vertical stripes in upper half :  Black \n
        Background : White \n
    </string>

    <!--marking-->

    <string name="isi_handling1">
        Name : Magnetized Material \n
        Cargo IMP Code : MAG \n
        Minimum Dimensions : 110 x 90 mm \n
        Color : Blue on White \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_handling2">
        Name : This Way Up \n
        Minimum Dimensions : 74 x 105 mm \n
        Color : Red or Black on a contrasting background \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_handling3">
        Name : Lithium Battery Label \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RLI, RLM, ELI \n
        Dimensions : 105 x 75 mm \n
        Color : the border on the label must have red diagonal hatchings. Text and symbol black on a contrasting background \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_handling4">
        Name : Keep away from heat \n
        Dimensions : 74 x 105 mm \n
        Color : Red and black on a white background or alternative colors \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_handling5">
        Name : Cargo Aircraft Only \n
        Cargo IMP Code : CAO \n
        Dimensions : 120 x110 mm \n
        Color : Black on Orangen \n
    </string>
    <string name="isi_handling6">
        Name : Cyrogenic Liquid \n
        Cargo IMP Code : RCL \n
        Minimum Dimensions : 75 x 105 mm \n
        Color : White on Green \n
    </string>

    <!--segregation-->

    <string name="isi_segregation1">
        Packages containing dangerous goods which may react dangerously with each other, must not be stowed on a aircraft next to each other on in position that allow interaction between them in the event of leakage.
        To maintain acceptable segregation between packages containing dangerous goods having different hazards, the segregation requirement shown on table below must be observed.
    </string>
    <string name="isi_segregation2">
        Notes : \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 1. An "x" at the intersection of a row and a column indicates that packages containing these classes/divisions of dangerous goods must be segregated.
        A "—" at the intersection of a row and column indicates that packages containing these classes/divisions of dangerous goods do not require segregations. \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 2. divisions 1.4 S , 4.1, and Class 6, 7, and 9 are not included on the table as they do not require segregation from other classes of dangerous goods. \n
    </string>

    <!--packing instruction-->

    <string name="judul_pi219">Packing Instructionn 219</string>
    <string name="judul_pi101">Packing Instructionn 101</string>
    <string name="judul_piy956">Packaging Instruction Y956</string>
    <string name="judul_pi114">Packing Instruction 114</string>
    <string name="judul_piy964">Packaging Instruction Y964</string>

    <string name="pi_219">
        This instruction applies to Class 2 adsorbed gases, UN 3512 to UN 3526 on passenger aircraft and/or Cargo Aircraft only, as applicable. \n

        For cylinders, the general packing requirements of 5.0.2 and 5.2.0 must be met. \n

        Cylinders contructed as specified in 6.4 and in accordance with ISO 11513:2011 or ISO 9809-1:2010 are permitted for the transport of adsorbed gases provided that: \n

        \t\t 101. The pressure of each filled cylinder must be less than 101.3 kPa at 20oC and less than 300 kPa at 50oC; \n
        \t\t 102. The minimum test pressure of the cylinder is 21 bar; \n
        \t\t 103. The minimum burst pressure of the cylinders is 94.5 bar; \n
        \t\t 104. The internal pressure at 65oC of the filled cylinder must no exceed the test pressure of the cylinder; \n
        \t\t 105. The adsorbent material must be compatible with the cylinder and must not form harmful or dangerous compounds with the gas to be adsorbed. The gas in combination with the adsorbent material must not affect or weaken the cylinder or cause a dangerous reaction (e.g. a catalyzing reaction); \n
        \t\t 106. The quality of the adsorbent must be verified at the time of each fill to assure the pressure and chemical stability requirements of this packing instruction are met each time an adsorbed gas package is offered for transport; \n
        \t\t 107. The adsorbent material must not meet the criteria of any of the classes or divisions in these Regulations; \n
        \t\t 108. The filling procedure must be in accordance with Annex A of ISO 11513:2011; \n
        \t\t 109. The maximum period for periodic inspections is five years; \n
        \t\t 110. The construction materials of the cylinders and their accessories must be compatible with the contents and must not react to form harmful or dangerous compounds therewith. \n
    </string>

    <string name="pi_101">
        STATE VARIATION: AEG-09, BEG-02, BHG-02/03, CAG-12, DQG-02, EGG-01, GBG-01, HKG-03, ITG-05, KGG-02, MYG-03, SAG-04, USG-05/15, ZAG-01 \n\n

        OPERATOR VARIATIONS: 5X-02/04, AH-02, AI-01, AM-01, BR-03, BZ-01, CA-11, D0-04, D5-01, ES-04, FX-01, GF-01/02, IG-01, IJ-01, IR-04, JJ-01, JU-02,KL-01, LY-04, MD-04, MH-11, MK-03, OU-11, PL-01, PR-01, PZ-01, QY-04, SQ-01, TU-01, UL-03, V3-01, VN-05, WY-02, XK-01 \n\n

        Packagings as specified by the appropriate national authority. \n

        The following statement must be marked on the Shipper’s Declaration for Dangerous Goods: “Packaging approved by the competent authority of XXX”, where “XXX” is the International Vehicle Registration Code (VRI Code) of the country which the authority acts. \n\n

        Note: \n

        In this the team “competent authority” is used for the intermodal compatibility; it refers to the appropriate national authority. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="pi_y956">
        STATE VARIATION: USG-04 \n\n

        OPERATOR VARIATIONS: AM-09, DE-01, FX-06, GA-03, GF-04, IJ-12, KC-11, LH-01, LX-02, MH-14, OS-03, OU-04, PX-10, SW-02, TN-04, UX-02, VO-03, VT-01, WY-04, XG-01, XK-03, XQ-01 \n\n

        This instruction applies to Limited Quantities of UN 3077 and UN 3335. \n\n

        The General Packing Requirements of Subsection 2.7.5, 5.0.2 to 5.0.4 (with the exception of 5.0.2.3, 5.0.2.5, 5.0.2.11 and 5.0.2.14.2) must be met except that the packagings do not have to meet the marking and testing requirements of 6.0.4 and Subsection 6.3. Packagings must meet the construction criteria specified in Subsection 6.1 and 6.2 and the test criteria specified in Subsection 6.6. \n\n

        Compatibility Requirements \n
        \t\t - Substances must be compatible with their packagings as required by 5.0.2.6. \n\n

        Closure Requirements \n

        \t\t - Closures must meet the requirements of 5.0.2.7. \n\n

        Limited Quantity Requirements \n\n

        The requirements of Subsection 2.7 must be met including: \n

        \t\t - the capability of the package to pass a drop test of 1.2 m; \n
        \t\t - a 24 hour stacking test; \n
        \t\t - the gross weight of the completed package must not exceed 30 kg. \n\n

        Single packagings are not permitted. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="pi_114">
        STATE VARIATION: AEG-09, BEG-02,BHG-02/03, CAG-12, DQG-02, EGG-01, GBG-01, HKG-03, ITG-05, KGG-02, MYG-03, SAG-04, USG-05/13, ZAG-01 \n\n

        OPERATOR VARIATIONS: 5X-02/04, AH-02, AI-01, AM-01, BR-03, BZ-01, CA-11, D0-04, D5-01, ES-04, FX-01, GF-01/02, IG-01, IJ-01, IR-04, JJ-01, JU-02, KL-01, LY-04, MD-04, MH-11, MK-03, OU-11, PL-01, PR-01, PZ-01, QY-04, SQ-01, TU-01, UL-03, V3-01, VN-05, WY-02, XK-01 \n\n

        This instruction applies to UN 0407, UN 0448, and UN 0509 on Cargo Aircraft Only. \n

        The General Packing Requirements of Subsection 5.0.2, 5.1.0 and 5.1.1 must be met. \n

        Unless otherwise provided for in these Regulation, packagings, must meet Packing Group II requirements. \n\n

        Wetted Solid: \n

        Wetted solid explosive may only be packed in accordance with this Packing Instruction under an exemption issued by the appropriated national authority of the State of origin. \n\n

        Dry Solid: \n

        Intermediate packagings are not required. \n\n

        Additional Packaging Requirements \n

        For UN 0509 metal packagings must be used. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="pi_y964">
        STATE VARIATION: USG-04 \n\n

        OPERATOR VARIATIONS: AM-09, DE-01, FX-06, GA-03, GF-04, IJ-12, KC-11, LH-01, LX-02, MH-14, OS-03, OU-04, PX-10, SW-02, TN-04, UX-02, VT-01, WY-04, XG-01, XK-03, XQ-01 \n\n

        This instruction applies to Limited Quantities of UN 1941, UN 1990, UN 3082 and UN 3334. \n\n

        Except for UN 3082, when the requirements of 5.0.2.9 do not apply; The General Packing Requirements of Subsections 2.7.5, 5.0.2, to 5.0.4 (with the exception of 5.0.2.3, 5.0.2.5, 5.0.2.11 and 5.0.2.14.2) must be met except that the packagings do not have to meet the marking and testing requirements of 6.0.4 and Subsection 6.3. Packagings must meet the construction criteria specified in Subsection 6.1 and 6.2 and the test criteria specified in Subsection 6.6. \n\n

        Compatibility Requirements \n
        \t\t - Substances must be compatible with their packagings as required by 5.0.2.6. \n\n

        Closure Requirements \n
        \t\t - Closures must meet the requirements of 5.0.2.7. \n\n

        Limited Quantity Requirements \n\n

        The requirements of Subsection 2.7 must be met including: \n

        \t\t - the capability of the package to pass a drop test of 1.2 m; \n
        \t\t - a 24 hour stacking test; \n
        \t\t - the gross weight of the completed package must not exceed 30 kg. \n\n

        Single packagings are not permitted. \n\n
    </string>

    <!--airline limitation-->

    <string name="cou_peru_1">
        Part 110, paragraph 110.5(h) of the Peruvian Aviation Regulations currently in force states that all air shipments of explosives including loads in transit must have a written authorization or exemption issued by the DGCA, as appropriate. Paragraph 110.5(i) sets out the requirements for the granting of authorizations and exemptions.
    </string>

    <string name="cou_peru_2">
        All shipments of dangerous goods that qualify as controlled products or chemical inputs by the terms of Law 28305 on Controlled Products and Chemical Inputs of Peru must comply with the provisions of said law.
    </string>

    <string name="cou_peru_3">
        Part 110, paragraph 110.37(d) of the Peruvian Aviation Regulations currently in force states that shippers offering dangerous goods for loading onto an aircraft must provide the air operator with copies of the safety information sheets for the goods to be shipped.

    </string>

    <string name="cou_spain_1">
        In domestic transport and in international transport originating in Spain, Spanish shall be used in all the markings and in the dangerous goods transport document, in addition to the languages required by the States of transit and destination.
    </string>

    <string name="cou_poland_1">
        Consignments containing spent nuclear fuel or radioactive waste transported to, from, through or over the territory of Poland are subject to prior written notification. Notification should be forwarded at least two weeks prior to shipment to: \n\n
        National Atomic Energy Agency (PAA) \n
        Department of Radiological Protection \n
        Krucza 36 Street \n
        00-522 Warsaw \n
        Poland \n\n
        Telephone: +48 22 695 97 43 \n
        Facsimile: +48 22 695 98 71 \n
        Email: sekretariat.dor@paa.gov.pl \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="cou_nepal_1">
        Operators intending to carry dangerous goods to, from, within and over Nepal must obtain prior written permission from the Director General, Civil Aviation Authority of Nepal. The requests for approval should be addressed to: \n\n

        Flight Safety Standards Department \n
        Civil Aviation Authority of Nepal \n

        Singamangal, Kathmandu \n

        NEPAL \n\n

        Telephone: +977-1-4111075/4111119 \n

        Facsimile: +977-1-4111198 \n

        Email: atsc@ccsl.com.np
    </string>

    <string name="cou_ukraine_1">
        The exportation, importation and transit of all radioactive material, without exceptions, are subject to the approval of the State Export Control Service of Ukraine and a decision from the Environmental Safety Ministry (State Nuclear Regulatory Administration of Ukraine). Any questions regarding this variation should be addressed to: \n\n

        State Export Committee of Ukraine \n
        19/21 Frunze Street \n
        Kiev, 254080 \n
        UKRAINE \n
        Telephone/facsimile: 044-4624970 \n\n
        or \n\n

        State Nuclear Regulatory Administration of Ukraine \n
        9/11 Arsenaina Street \n
        Kiev, 01011 \n
        UKRAINE \n
        Telephone: 044-2944224 \n
        Facsimile: (044) 2948895 \n\n
    </string>

    <!--airline limitation-->

    <string name="air_virginia_1">
        Petrol powered equipment, such as chainsaws, brush cutters, generators or the like, either new or used, are forbidden in carry on or checked in baggage. Such items will only be accepted as cargo if they are packaged and shipped in accordance with IATA dangerous goods regulations where special provision A70 applies to internal combustion or fuel cells engines, these items may be accepted for transport as cargo provided operator approval has been granted. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_virginia_2">
        Dangerous goods listed in the list of high consequence dangerous goods will not be accepted. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_virginia_3">
        Lithium ion batteries UN 3480 are prohibited for carriage as cargo. This prohibition does not apply to : \n\n

        - UN 3481 Lithium ion contained in or packed with equipment. \n

        - UN 3091 Lithium metal batteries in or packed with equipment. \n

        - Lithium batteries (rechargeable and non-rechargeable) covered by the provisions  for dangerous goods carried by passenger or crew. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_tnt_1">
        Dangerous goods in TNT Express Air Network (including UN 3480 and UN 3090, section 1A, 1B and II), will be accepted from approved customers only after TNT and Customer have agreed on specific dangerous goods related requirements and conditions. Contact the local TNT office for detail of this requirements as well as the application procedure for the “approved customer status”. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_tnt_2">
        Lithium ion and lithium metal batteries in TNT’s General Cargo Service : \n\n
        
        - UN 3480 and UN 3090 of section II are strictly forbidden; \n
        
        - UN 3480 and UN 3090 of section IA and IB are subject to prior approval. A copy of the Shipper’s Declaration and the UN test report must be provided at the time of booking. \n
        
        - UN 3481 and UN 3091, all Sections are acceptable if in compliance with the IATA DGR. \n
    </string>

    <string name="air_philair_1">
        Only the following dangerous goods under class 1 – explosive, division 1.4S are acceptable to Philipine Airlines for air carriage \n\n
        UN Number –description \n
        UN 0012—Cartridges for weapons, inert projectile [130] \n
        UN 0012—Cartridges small arms [130] \n
        UN 0014 – Cartridges for weapons, blank [130] \n
        UN 0014—Cartridges small arms, blank [130] \n
        UN 0044—Primers, cap type [133] \n
        UN 0055—Cases, cartridges , empty, with primer [136] \n
        UN 0405—Cartridges, signal [135] \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_philair_2">
        Fuel containers for camping stoves that have contained a flammable liquid fuel shall not be accepted for carriage as checked baggage \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_philair_3">
        UN 3480—Lithium ion batteries, PI 965 section IA, section IB, section II will not be accepted for carriage as cargo \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_jetstar_1">
        Not Used. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_jetstar_2">
        Division 4.1 Flammable Solids. Passengers and crew are not permitted to bring book matches onto aircraft for personal use. Book matches are only allowed as correctly packed and declared dangerous goods consignment (see 2.3.5.6) \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_jetstar_3">
        Operator approval is required for the carriage of all new and used internal combustion engines (see.2.3.5.15) \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_jetstar_4">
        Oxygen or air, gaseous cylinders required for medical use are only accepted for transport in or as carryon baggage (see 2.3.4.1) \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_jetstar_5">
        Dangerous Goods in consolidation will not be accepted for carriage except for UN 1845 Carbon dioxide solid/dry ice up to maximum of 145 kg per flight when used as refrigerant for non-dangerous goods consignment. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_czech_1">
        Dangerous goods as defined in these regulations will not be accepted in air mail. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_czech_2">
        Not Used. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_czech_3">
        Fissile radioactive material will not be accepted  for carriage. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_czech_4">
        Liquid dangerous goods packed in single metal packagings (1A1, 1A2, 1B1, 1B2) will not be accepted unless safety overpacked to protect the base of the packaging. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="air_czech_5">
        Small oxygen cylinders containing gaseous oxygen or air required for medical use are not permitted on the person, in checked or carry on baggage. Czech Airlines provide oxygen cylinders on request of passenger during flight booking, but at least 48 hours in advance. \n\n
    </string>

    <!--<menu utama>-->

    <string name="welcome">
        Find Your Air Cargo Shipping Guidelines Information That You Need Here \n\n
        Visit Our Website On \n
    </string>


    <!--about-->

    <string name="about_apk">
        ACS GUIDELINES \n
        Aplikasi Informasi Pedoman Pengiriman Barang Lintas Udara \n\n\n

        Dibuat Oleh : \n
        M. LUTFI NURMALIK WARAQA \n
        57414400 \n\n\n

        Teknik Informatika \n
        Universitas Gunadarma \n
        2018 \n
    </string>

    <string name="contact">
        Please Contact Us on : \n\n

        (021) 5677754 \n
        contact@dgregulations.com \n
        www.dgregulations.com \n\n

        Or you can send message us below : \n\n
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
