<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ACS Guidelines</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="tanya_regis">Do Not Have An Account? </string>
    <string name="registrasi">Register Here</string>
    <string name="persetujuan">I Am Responsible That The Data I Entered Is Correct</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_logout">Log Out</string>
    <string name="linkdg"><u>www.dgregulations.com</u></string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="type_name">Type Name</string>
    <string-array name="spinner_gender">
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="isi_dg">
         Dangerous goods are articles or subtances which are capable of posing a significant risk to health, safety or to property when transported by air.
    </string>

    <string name="isi_limit">
         Limitation explain about procedures and rules for sending dangerous goods from various airlines and countries.
    </string>

    <!--segregation-->

    <string name="isi_segregation1">
        Packages containing dangerous goods which may react dangerously with each other, must not be stowed on a aircraft next to each other on in position that allow interaction between them in the event of leakage.
        To maintain acceptable segregation between packages containing dangerous goods having different hazards, the segregation requirement shown on table below must be observed.
    </string>
    <string name="isi_segregation2">
        Notes : \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 1. An "x" at the intersection of a row and a column indicates that packages containing these classes/divisions of dangerous goods must be segregated.
        A "—" at the intersection of a row and column indicates that packages containing these classes/divisions of dangerous goods do not require segregations. \n\n
        \t\t\t\t 2. divisions 1.4 S , 4.1, and Class 6, 7, and 9 are not included on the table as they do not require segregation from other classes of dangerous goods. \n
    </string>

    <!--<menu utama>-->

    <string name="welcome">
        Get The Information Of Air Cargo Shipping Guidelines That You Need \n\n
        Visit Our Website On \n
    </string>


    <!--about-->

    <string name="about_apk">
        ACS GUIDELINES \n
        Aplikasi Informasi Pedoman Pengiriman Barang Lintas Udara \n\n\n

        Dibuat Oleh : \n
        M. LUTFI NURMALIK WARAQA \n
        57414400 \n\n\n

        Teknik Informatika \n
        Universitas Gunadarma \n
        2018 \n
    </string>

    <string name="contact">
        Please Contact Us on : \n\n

        www.dgregulations.com \n\n

        Or you can send message us below : \n\n
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
